fquiz_data = [
    {
        "question": "What environment do fish live in?",
        "choices": ["Land", "Air", "Water", "Fire"],
        "answer": "Water"
    },
    {
        "question": "What covers a fish's body like armor, protecting them?",
        "choices": ["Feathers", "Scales", "Fur", "Skin"],
        "answer": "Scales"
    },
    {
        "question": "What do fish use to breathe underwater?",
        "choices": ["Lungs", "Gills", "Noses", "Mouths"],
        "answer": "Gills"
    },
    {
        "question": "Where do some fish, like goldfish and bettas, live?",
        "choices": ["In salty ocean water", "In freshwater rivers and lakes", "In deserts", "In trees"],
        "answer": "In freshwater rivers and lakes"
    },
    {
        "question": "What do fish use to steer, balance, and move through the water?",
        "choices": ["Gills", "Fins", "Tails", "Feathers"],
        "answer": "Fins"
    },
    {
        "question": "What do fish use to take oxygen from the water?",
        "choices": ["Lungs", "Gills", "Noses", "Mouths"],
        "answer": "Gills"
    },
    {
        "question": "What do some fish have instead of bones?",
        "choices": ["Steel", "Wood", "Cartilage", "Feathers"],
        "answer": "Cartilage"
    },
    {
        "question": "What can fish do to move quickly through the water?",
        "choices": ["Shoot water out of their mouths", "Shoot water out of their gills", "Fly", "Swim"],
        "answer": "Shoot water out of their gills"
    },
    {
        "question": "What do fish use to blend in with their surroundings?",
        "choices": ["Fins", "Tails", "Colors and patterns", "Eyespots"],
        "answer": "Colors and patterns"
    },
    {
        "question": "What do some fish have near their tails that look like eyes?",
        "choices": ["Fins", "Tails", "Eyespots", "Mouths"],
        "answer": "Eyespots"
    }



]